{
    "subject": "resource/AJ_Michalka",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1991-04-10",
    "human_readable": "AJ Michalka was born on April 10, 1991.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9018779993057251,
            "question": "When was AJ Michalka born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8479406237602234,
            "question": "Where was AJ Michalka born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8221084475517273,
            "question": "What is AJ Michalka's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4980265498161316,
            "question": "Is AJ Michalka a singer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48096397519111633,
            "question": "In what year did AJ Michalka come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4634891748428345,
            "question": "What is AJ Michalka best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35203811526298523,
            "question": "Has AJ Michalka appeared in any movies or television shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33781182765960693,
            "question": "Is AJ Michalka a member of any musical groups?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23494169116020203,
            "question": "What kind of music does AJ Michalka perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20861051976680756,
            "question": "Does AJ Michalka play any musical instruments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=AJ Michalka was born on April 10, 1991.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9254_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does AJ Michalka perform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9254_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is AJ Michalka a member of any musical groups?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9254_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has AJ Michalka appeared in any movies or television shows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9254_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9254_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain multiple entries with information about AJ Michalka's birthdate, which consistently mention her birth on April 10, 1991. Therefore, the triple \"AJ Michalka was born on April 10, 1991\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that Amanda Joy \"AJ\" Michalka (born April 10, 1991) is an American actress, singer-songwriter, and musician. This information supports the statement that AJ Michalka was born on April 10, 1991."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}